This is probably the first time in your life
ربما تكون هذه هي المرة الأولى في حياتك
that the virus has gone out of control.
أن الفيروس قد خرج عن السيطرة.
So this is how unbearable it feels.
إذن، هذا هو مدى صعوبة الشعور.
You even run a fever.
بل إنك تعاني من ارتفاع في درجة الحرارة.
So that night in the original timeline,
في تلك الليلة في الجدول الزمني الأصلي،
you forced yourself to endure it alone.
أجبرت نفسك على تحمل ذلك بمفردك.
It must have been far worse than this.
لا بد أن الأمر كان أسوأ من ذلك بكثير.
He can't even get up.
لا يستطيع حتى النهوض.
Let's not waste the food.
دعونا لا نهدر الطعام.
You're such a noisy eater.
أنت تأكل بصوت عالٍ جداً.
This is all because of you.
كل هذا بفضلك.
This bread's no good now.
هذا الخبز لم يعد صالحاً للاستخدام.
Stay.
يقضي.
Your scent helps me fall asleep.
رائحتك تساعدني على النوم.
Hey.
يا.
This is Xu's first time being in love.
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي يقع فيها شو في الحب.
Let him have his way this once.
دعه يفعل ما يشاء هذه المرة.
We'll give him a proper talking-to tomorrow.
سنوبخه بشدة غداً.
That noise just now really wasn't me.
لم يكن ذلك الصوت الذي سمعته للتو صوتي أنا.
Your mother probably knocked something over
ربما أسقطت والدتك شيئًا ما.
while she was cleaning.
أثناء قيامها بالتنظيف.
I'll go take a look.
سأذهب لألقي نظرة.
If you're not feeling well,
إذا لم تكن تشعر بحالة جيدة،
get some more sleep.
احصل على قسط إضافي من النوم.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Someone's outside the window.
هناك شخص ما خارج النافذة.
I saw that person
رأيت ذلك الشخص
near your place yesterday.
بالقرب من مكانك أمس.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
That couple refused to hand over Xie Xinxu,
رفض ذلك الزوجان تسليم شي شينشو،
so we took action.
لذلك اتخذنا إجراءً.
Now the situation has changed.
لقد تغير الوضع الآن.
We need your instructions for the next step.
نحتاج إلى تعليماتك للخطوة التالية.
We haven't searched the house yet,
لم نفتش المنزل بعد،
but our people have already surrounded it.
لكن رجالنا قد حاصروها بالفعل.
Xie Xinxu is definitely still inside.
من المؤكد أن شي شينشو لا تزال بالداخل.
Understood.
مفهوم.
We'll pull back for now.
سنتراجع في الوقت الحالي.
We'll wait for the rest of the Bureau team to arrive and take over.
سننتظر وصول بقية فريق المكتب وتوليهم زمام الأمور.
What did he just say?
ماذا قال للتو؟
Something about taking action?
شيء ما يتعلق باتخاذ إجراء؟
Stay in the room.
ابقَ في الغرفة.
I'll go check outside.
سأذهب لأتفقد الأمر من الخارج.
This is the day Xie Xinxu's parents died.
هذا هو اليوم الذي توفي فيه والدا شي شينشو.
It's also the day we first met.
إنه أيضاً اليوم الذي التقينا فيه لأول مرة.
Then doesn't that mean my brother and the others
ألا يعني ذلك أن أخي والآخرين
will be here soon to take Xie Xinxu in as a suspect?
هل سيأتي أحدٌ قريباً ليقبض على شي شينكسو كمشتبه به؟
It's best not to touch anything.
من الأفضل عدم لمس أي شيء.
Preserve every trace at the scene.
حافظ على كل أثر في مكان الحادث.
And this knife.
وهذه السكين.
Your fingerprints are on it.
بصمات أصابعك موجودة عليه.
That would be hard to explain.
سيكون من الصعب شرح ذلك.
Your expression too.
تعبيرك أيضاً.
You don't look like someone who's grieving at all.
لا تبدو كشخص يعاني من الحزن على الإطلاق.
That's how they'll mark you as a suspect.
هكذا سيصنفونك كمشتبه به.
That kind of grieving look you mentioned,
ذلك النوع من نظرة الحزن التي ذكرتها،
I don't think I can do it.
لا أعتقد أنني أستطيع فعل ذلك.
I almost forgot.
كادت أن تفوتني.
He has emotional blunting.
يعاني من تبلد المشاعر.
Onions.
البصل.
Cutting onions makes people tear up.
تقطيع البصل يجعل الناس يذرفون الدموع.
That won't work.
هذا لن ينجح.
See?
يرى؟
It works.
إنها تعمل.
You do the cutting yourself.
أنت تقوم بالقص بنفسك.
We're running out of time!
الوقت ينفد!
They lay there without a breath,
استلقوا هناك بلا نفس،
and I was shedding tears that weren't real.
وكنت أذرف دموعاً لم تكن حقيقية.
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Isn't that cruelly ironic?
أليس هذا تناقضاً قاسياً؟
Grief isn't expressed only through tears.
لا يُعبَّر عن الحزن بالدموع فقط.
Just like how you usually get along,
تماماً كما هو الحال عادةً،
you're not very direct with your emotions either.
أنت أيضاً لست صريحاً جداً في التعبير عن مشاعرك.
But
لكن
I can feel the love you have for each other
أشعر بالحب الذي يكنه كل منكما للآخر
through the subtle ways you show it.
من خلال الطرق الدقيقة التي تُظهر بها ذلك.
Take him away.
خذوه بعيداً.
Look here!
انظر هنا!
Please stand back.
يرجى التراجع.
Please answer our questions!
يرجى الإجابة على أسئلتنا!
- Can you please give us an answer? - Please answer!
- هل يمكنك أن تعطينا إجابة من فضلك؟ - أرجو الإجابة!
Stand back!
تراجعوا!
Please answer our questions!
يرجى الإجابة على أسئلتنا!
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك.
Xie Xinxu!
شكرا لك، شينكسو!
Nongyu!
نونجيو!
[Practice Book Name: Wu Nongyu Class: Class 1, Grade 5]
[اسم كتاب التدريبات: وو نونغيو، الصف: الصف الأول، المستوى الخامس]
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Why are you in my room?
لماذا أنت في غرفتي؟
Why did you call my name?
لماذا ناديت باسمي؟
So bad guys can actually be this good-looking.
إذن، يمكن أن يكون الأشرار بهذا القدر من الوسامة.
Are you
أنت
Wu Nongyu?
وو نونجيو؟
Big guy,
رجل ضخم،
what kind of bad guy
أي نوع من الأشرار
is as silly as you?
هل هو سخيف مثلك؟
You were just looking for me,
كنت تبحث عني فقط،
and now you don't even recognize me.
والآن أنت لا تتعرف عليّ حتى.
Blood!
دم!
Why doesn't my gunshot wound hurt?
لماذا لا يؤلمني جرحي الناتج عن إطلاق النار؟
Is this really the real world?
هل هذا هو العالم الحقيقي حقاً؟
No wonder you're acting a bit slow.
لا عجب أنك تتصرف ببطء بعض الشيء.
Some other bad people must have hurt you,
لا بد أن بعض الأشخاص السيئين الآخرين قد آذوك.
and you hit your head and lost your memory.
وارتطم رأسك بالأرض وفقدت ذاكرتك.
You forgot how to get home,
لقد نسيت كيف تعود إلى المنزل،
so you kept running,
لذا واصلت الركض،
and ended up in my room.
وانتهى بي الأمر في غرفتي.
Right?
يمين؟
Drink this. It'll help with the pain.
اشرب هذا. سيساعدك على تخفيف الألم.
I don't usually share this with people.
لا أشارك هذا الأمر مع الناس عادةً.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Why did you give me
لماذا أعطيتني
medicated oil to drink?
هل يُشرب زيت طبي؟
It's actually a really good drink.
إنه مشروب جيد حقاً.
You really don't know how to appreciate it.
أنت حقاً لا تعرف كيف تقدر ذلك.
Or you could drink my blood instead.
أو يمكنك أن تشرب دمي بدلاً من ذلك.
My dad says my blood is really powerful.
يقول والدي إن دمي قوي جداً.
Why are there so many needle marks on your arm?
لماذا توجد كل هذه الآثار الناتجة عن الإبر على ذراعك؟
Did someone bully you?
هل تعرضت للتنمر من قبل أحد؟
It was my dad.
كان والدي.
Big guy,
رجل ضخم،
just hide yourself.
اختبئ فقط.
Don't make a sound, okay?
لا تُصدر أي صوت، حسناً؟
I'll protect you.
سأحميك.
What took you so long to open the door?
ما الذي أخّرك كل هذا الوقت لفتح الباب؟
Ever since we entered Sunset Forest,
منذ أن دخلنا غابة الغروب،
time and space have been completely scrambled.
لقد تم تشويه الزمان والمكان بشكل كامل.
I have to figure out what's going on.
عليّ أن أفهم ما يحدث.
This is definitely not the real world.
هذا بالتأكيد ليس العالم الحقيقي.
Big guy.
رجل ضخم.
Can you sneak me away?
هل يمكنك أن تهرب بي؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Dad found us.
أبي وجدنا.
Up the stairs.
صعود الدرج.
[Vanity Mirror]
[مرآة الغرور]
Keep going up.
استمر في الصعود.
To the right.
إلى اليمين.
There's a scarf my mom knitted for me in my backpack.
يوجد وشاح حيكته أمي لي في حقيبة ظهري.
I need to take it with me.
أحتاج أن آخذه معي.
Hurry. Dad's about to catch up.
أسرعوا. أبي على وشك اللحاق بنا.
Nongyu.
نونجيو.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪